http://www.cpcinsurance.net/privacy-policy

Skip to content
405-843-56781140 Northwest 50th StreetOklahoma City, OK 73118 Se habla Español Toggle navigation
HomeInsuranceClaims & ServiceBlogAboutContactPrivacy Policy CPC Insurance Agency, IncWhat information do we collect? We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or social security number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will be kept on file for more than 60 days in order to provide continued customer service..Do we use cookies? Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party links Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on 10/25/2010Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. PO Box 18444 Oklahoma City, Oklahoma 73118 USA cpc [at] cpcinsurance [dot] com 405-843-5678 Get a QuoteGive us some info and we'll get quotes from multiple companies.Get a Quote
Toggle Dropdown AutoHomeownerLifeMotorcycleBusinessMore…Insurance Partners
From Our Blog Don’t Delay — Start Thinking About Winterizing Your RV Today December 4, 2020
10 Things to do to Prepare Your Home for Fall November 6, 2020
It’s Back-to-School Time — Is Your House Ready? October 2, 2020
Connect OnlineAbout Us CPC Insurance Agency, Inc is an independent insurance agency located in Oklahoma City, Oklahoma. Give us a call, stop by, or request a quote online to find out how much we can save you on your insurance.HomeAboutContactSitemapRecent Articles Don’t Delay — Start Thinking About Winterizing Your RV Today December 4, 2020
10 Things to do to Prepare Your Home for Fall November 6, 2020
It’s Back-to-School Time — Is Your House Ready? October 2, 2020 Quick LinksAbout UsContact UsService CenterInsurance ProductsGet an Insurance QuoteCompanies We RepresentStaff DirectoryContact Us 1140 Northwest 50th StreetOklahoma City, OK 73118 405-843-5678 405-843-5782 cpc [at] cpcinsurance [dot] com cpc [at] cpcinsurance [dot] com Mon-Fri 8:30am-4:30pmClosed 12pm - 1pm © 2020 CPC Insurance Agency, Inc | Search | Privacy | Disclaimer | Website by BT
